<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SKKU Software forum</title>
    <link>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SKKU Software forum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:07:30 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://skkuoverflow.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skkuoverflow.com/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inuiyeji cluster</title>
      <link>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/inuiyeji/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:07:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/inuiyeji/</guid>
      <description>What is Inuiyeji cluster? &amp;lsquo;Inuiyeji&amp;rsquo; cluster is a server cluster that is available for SKKU students who major in Software Engineering. Currently the &amp;lsquo;In&amp;rsquo; server is runs independently, and the &amp;lsquo;uiyeji&amp;rsquo; server is bounded with nfs.
Translation of the below notice about the server. (https://cs.skku.edu/news/notice/view/2587)
4-node Linux cluster server is now available for SW college students.
Students who want to use it can use it freely.
Hosts:
- swin.skku.edu - swui.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux commands</title>
      <link>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:07:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/linux/</guid>
      <description>Basic Linux Commands   Information  Commands that are applicable to both files and directories typically require additional options when attempting to apply to directories. Please check the options before you apply them. Please refer to the table below for other notations.     Notation Meaning     (&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;-) Additional Options (Not required)   [&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;] Required Options   usage Links to more detailed explanations      Linux filesystem    Command Description Example Man page Usage     ls (option) (directory) View the contents of (directory) ls Link Link   cd (directory) Navigate through (directory) cd Test/ Link Link   mkdir [name] Make a new directory with the name [name] mkdir Test Link    cp (option) [name1] [name2] Copy name1 files/directories to name2 files/directories cp test1 test2 Link    mv (option) [name1] [name2] Move name1 file to name2 file mv file1 Test/file2 Link    rm (option) [name] Delete files/directories called [name] rm file1 Link Link   cat (option) (filename) List [filename] contents cat file1 Link Link      Linux package manager   Before we start&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobaxterm</title>
      <link>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/mobaxterm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:07:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skkuoverflow.com/posts/mobaxterm/</guid>
      <description>How to use Mobaxterm Mobaxterm is a program that supports running remote programs such as ssh, sftp, and X11 forwarding. Mobaxterm has a free and paid version, but the free version is more than enough. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to install:
 Go to https://mobaxterm.mobatek.net/ to download and install the installer. Open the program. Press &amp;lsquo;session&amp;rsquo; at the top left. Press the leftmost &amp;lsquo;ssh&amp;rsquo; and set it up.   remote host: (Example) swji.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
